Music
Hello, we're Ukka
♪ Music
Music
Our stage presence, with its solid singing ability and high quality music...
We are known in the idol world for our nostalgic, sweet and sour sound.
Ukka will be performing the music video for her new song
Blow Up Days music video was shot here in Osaka.
The first half of the music video is an off-shot style music video.
The staff prepared this music video for us.
Enjoying a somewhat nostalgic, sweet and sour tour
The first half of the music video is an off-shot style, so the staff has prepared some shots of us in our natural state.
Sora Akane and Ruri Aoi are in charge of the camera.
I'm taking pictures with Sora!
Oh! They usually take pictures of us, don't they?
I've been looking for a camera lately.
I wanted to get the Sony camera that the photographer has.
We don't work together, so...
I'd like to take a shot here and there.
I won't.
Here we go!
Cheese!
Quick, quick, quick!
A nostalgic, sweet and sour tour. Where's the first spot?
This one!
It is a store that stands out even in the Tsutenkaku area where there are many coffee shops, and it is a Showa Heritage site famous for having been the setting of a commercial shooting and a popular cartoon in the past.
Here it is! Thank you very much!
Lesca is amazing! Lemon squash!
I just said that a while ago. Lesca is lemon squash?
It's on the foie gras bag too! I only drink it when it's on special!
Bon appétit!
It's strong!
You squeezed too much!
What's the recipe for lemon squash?
It's sour!
Yes, it is!
But it's really refreshing!
It tastes so good!
Old-fashioned lemon syrup to adjust the sweetness!
Now that we've got that extra sourness off the top that could be used in a music video...
Yes, solo part Trowker!
Oh no, the next one that makes my heart skip a beat!
Naturalness adds even more cuteness to the music video
Solo Part Trowker System
Here's who's nominated
Solo part lip scene often seen in music videos
In short, you can try looking at the camera like this
Reward time with a strong element of recklessness
I've just been given a sour drink.
Ruri-san, who has ruined her visuals
Let's go!
Part A
Pretending to be a good girl in the melody
the part where you always pretend to be a good girl
Shall we do it, Jaari-san?
Let's be a little cute.
It's cute.
Here we go, don't forget.
Okay, that's it.
Embarrassing.
There's a lot of people here, and it's a little weird.There are a lot of people here.
It's true that the song is twice as good as the original, so you don't have to take it in stride while being watched by so many sound people.
I'll give it eight shots, but I also have feelings for you.
Don't worry, the sour experience of Lesca alone won't put the horses to shame, so we'll have to get Pisserbrother's sweet specialties too.
Yes!
Thank you very much for this limited menu of Kikka Brother's. It's a sweet pudding against a sour one.
I like the sweet pudding.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I won't eat it, I won't eat it!
I'd like you to try this place!
I'm sorry, I have a cold.
Then I'll do the big one.
A little bangs!
A little bangs.
I'm going to cut them.
Okay, yes!
I've been hiding myself.
Before I knew it, I was making up smiles.
I've gotten so good at it, they don't even notice I'm hurting.
They don't even notice.
I'm really, really stuck on it.
It's really, really good.
Somewhere between soft and hard.
It's much easier to get stuck.
It's important.
Thank you so much.
It was really good today.